fm-teens.com 2016-05-15

# Privacy Policy

### Acceptance of this Privacy Policy

By using the web site or any services provided through the web site, you expressly consent to the use and disclosure of information as described in this Privacy Policy. FM-TEENS.COM may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. Any changes will be posted to this site, so we encourage you to continuously review our Privacy Policy. All Privacy Policy changes will take effect immediately upon their posting on this Website. Your continued use of FM-TEENS.COM Services or acceptance of our e-mails following the posting of changes to these terms will indicate your acceptance of these changes.

### Personal Information

FM-TEENS.COM allows you to visit the website without revealing any personal information about yourself. Your visit to this website is anonymous.

The information you provide will not be used for any commercial purposes and will not be sold, rented, leased or otherwise forwarded to any third party. We do not distribute or share your personal information beyond what is strictly necessary to fulfill our obligations to you, and then only with partners who adhere to FM-TEENS.COM's commitment to protecting your privacy and data. FM-TEENS.COM may provide your personal information if necessary, in FM-TEENS.COM’s good faith judgment, to comply with laws or regulations of a governmental or regulatory body or in response to a valid subpoena, warrant, or order or to protect the rights of FM-TEENS.COM or others.

### Email Newsletter and Opt-Out

When submitting your e-mail address to FM-TEENS.COM, your e-mail address will automatically be added to our E-Newsletter Subscriber List, which we use to send out special offers or updates that may be of interest to you. FM-TEENS.COM will not sell, rent, or lease your personal information to non-partner entities. Users may choose not to participate in our mailing program, however. If you no longer wish to receive FM-TEENS.COM communications, you may "unsubscribe" from our mailing program at any time by clicking the auto-unsubscribe link in our emails. Our database will then be updated and no further email will be sent to the email address.

### Support

FM-TEENS.COM provides email support for users who have valid subscribtions. FM-TEENS.COM does not currently provide telephone support. If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or our information handling practices, please contact us through email. We will do our best to respond to your inquiry within two business days.
